<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="seriousGames.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE seriousGamesCatalog SYSTEM "seriousGames.dtd" [
    <!NOTATION JPG SYSTEM "image/jpeg">
    <!ENTITY reMission2Cover SYSTEM "images/re-mission2_cover.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY reMission2Screenshot1 SYSTEM "images/re-mission2_screeshot.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY reMission2Screenshot2 SYSTEM "images/re-mission2_screeshot2.jpg" NDATA JPG>

    <!ENTITY simCityCover SYSTEM "images/simcity_cover.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY simCityScreenshot1 SYSTEM "images/simcity_screenshot1.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY simCityScreenshot2 SYSTEM "images/simcity_screenshot2.jpg" NDATA JPG>

    <!ENTITY folditCover SYSTEM "images/foldit_cover.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY folditScreenshot1 SYSTEM "images/foldit_screenshot1.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY folditScreenshot2 SYSTEM "images/foldit_screenshot2.jpg" NDATA JPG>

    <!ENTITY factorioCover SYSTEM "images/factorio_cover.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY factorioScreenshot1 SYSTEM "images/factorio_screenshot1.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY factorioScreenshot2 SYSTEM "images/factorio_screenshot2.jpg" NDATA JPG>

    <!ENTITY minecraftCover SYSTEM "images/minecraft_cover.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY minecraftScreenshot1 SYSTEM "images/minecraft_screenshot1.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY minecraftScreenshot2 SYSTEM "images/minecraft_screenshot2.jpg" NDATA JPG>

    <!ENTITY flightSimulatorCover SYSTEM "images/microsoft_flight_simulator_cover.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY flightSimulatorScreenshot1 SYSTEM "images/microsoft_flight_simulator_screenshot1.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY flightSimulatorScreenshot2 SYSTEM "images/microsoft_flight_simulator_screenshot2.jpg" NDATA JPG>

    <!ENTITY dragonBoxElementsCover SYSTEM "images/dragonBox_cover.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY dragonBoxElementsScreenshot1 SYSTEM "images/dragonBox_screenshot1.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY dragonBoxElementsScreenshot2 SYSTEM "images/dragonBox_screenshot2.jpg" NDATA JPG>

    <!ENTITY hopelabLogo SYSTEM "images/hopelab.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY glasslabLogo SYSTEM "images/glasslabLogo.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY uwCseLogo SYSTEM "images/uwCse_logo.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY wubeLogo SYSTEM "images/wube_logo.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY mojangLogo SYSTEM "images/mojang_logo.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY microsoftLogo SYSTEM "images/microsoft_logo.jpg" NDATA JPG>
    <!ENTITY dragonBoxLogo SYSTEM "images/kahoot_dragonbox_logo.jpg" NDATA JPG>
]>

<seriousGamesCatalog>
    <genres>
        <genre id="gamesForHealth">
            <name>Games for Health</name>
            <description>
                Serious games for health (or “health games”) are games with a focus on health care, physical and mental fitness. In most cases,
                they are not commercial products but offered free by health care institutions like insurances, medical institutes, or foundations.
            </description>
        </genre>

        <genre id="advergames">
            <name>Advergames</name>
            <description>
                Games created for advertising or marketing purposes. An advertgame is a game that includes advert references designed to promote
                a given brand. This kind of medium, based on entertainment, makes it possible to capture prospects by means other than traditional media.
            </description>
        </genre>

        <genre id="gamesForTraining">
            <name>Games for Training</name>
            <description>
                Games for Training are a category of serious games explicitly developed to facilitate learning, skill development, and
                training in diverse domains. These games go beyond traditional educational methods by incorporating interactive and immersive elements,
                making the learning experience more engaging and effective.
            </description>
        </genre>

        <genre id="gamesForEducation">
            <name>Games for education</name>
            <description>
                Serious Games for Education form a genre of interactive digital experiences designed specifically for educational purposes.
                Unlike traditional educational methods, these games leverage technology and game mechanics to engage learners in a dynamic and
                immersive learning environment. The primary goal is to make learning enjoyable, fostering a deeper understanding of academic
                subjects and practical skills.
            </description>
        </genre>

        <genre id="gamesForScienceAndResearch">
            <name>Games for science and research</name>
            <description>
                Serious Games for Science and Research represent a genre of digital games designed to support scientific exploration,
                research, and educational initiatives within various scientific disciplines.
                These games are developed to engage players in scientific concepts, experiments, and research processes, fostering a deeper
                understanding of complex subjects.
            </description>
        </genre>

        <genre id="gamesForProduction">
            <name>Games for production</name>
            <description>
                Serious Games for Production are digital simulations or interactive experiences designed to enhance productivity, efficiency,
                and safety within industrial and production environments. These games are tailored for workers, operators, and managers involved in
                manufacturing, assembly, logistics, and other production-related activities.
                The primary objectives include skill development, process optimization, and fostering a culture of continuous improvement.
            </description>
        </genre>

        <genre id="gamesAsWork ">
            <name>Games as work</name>
            <description>
                Serious Games for Work are interactive digital experiences created to address specific professional development needs within
                a workplace.
                These games aim to enhance skills, improve job performance, and foster a positive work environment.
                Tailored to various industries and job roles, they provide an engaging and effective means of training and skill development.
            </description>
        </genre>
    </genres>

    <alluvialAreas>
        <area id="governmentNgo">
            <name>Government and NGO</name>
            <description>
                Games used in Public sector and non-governmental organizations.
            </description>
        </area>

        <area id="defense">
            <name>Defense</name>
            <description>
                Games used for defense and military training.
            </description>
        </area>

        <area id="healthcare">
            <name>Healthcare</name>
            <description>
                Games used in the healthcare sector for training or therapeutic purposes.
            </description>
        </area>

        <area id="marketingCommunication">
            <name>Marketing and Communication</name>
            <description>
                Games focused on promoting and advancing marketing and communication strategies.
                This includes simulations for advertising, public relations, and strategic communication campaigns.
            </description>
        </area>

        <area id="education">
            <name>Education</name>
            <description>
                Games designed for educational purposes, spanning a wide range of subjects and skills. These games aim to enhance
                learning experiences, engage students, and provide effective educational tools for various levels of education.
            </description>
        </area>

        <area id="corporate">
            <name>Corporate</name>
            <description>
                Games tailored for corporate training, team building, and professional development.
                These games aim to improve workplace skills, enhance collaboration, and address specific needs within the corporate environment.
            </description>
        </area>

        <area id="industry">
            <name>Industry</name>
            <description>
                Games developed for industrial and manufacturing sectors. These games may focus on training for specific industry processes,
                safety protocols, and operational procedures to enhance efficiency and reduce risks in industrial settings.
            </description>
        </area>
    </alluvialAreas>

    <creators>
        <creator id="hopelab">
            <name>Hopelab</name>
            <description>
                Hopelab is a social innovation lab focused on designing science-based technologies to improve the health and well-being of
                teens and young adults. They are a 501 private operating foundation based in San Francisco, California.
            </description>
            <logo src="hopelabLogo" />
        </creator>

        <creator id="glasslab">
            <name>Glasslab</name>
            <description>
                GlassLab reflects a major shift in the way students learn and acquire knowledge. Students today are expected to learn new skills,
                such as creative problem solving, collaboration and systems thinking, and master new technologies.
                GlassLab will address these new challenges by exploring how digital games can be effective environments for learning and make learning
                more relevant by connecting it with students’ interests.
            </description>
            <logo src="glasslabLogo" />
        </creator>

        <creator id="uwCse">
            <name>University of Washington Computer Science and Engineering</name>
            <description>
                The University of Washington's Computer Science and Engineering department is dedicated to advancing computer science and
                engineering through research and education.
            </description>
            <logo src="uwCseLogo" />
        </creator>

        <creator id="wubeSoftware">
            <name>Wube Software</name>
            <description>
                Wube Software is the developer of Factorio, a game development company passionate about creating engaging and challenging
                experiences for players.
            </description>
            <logo src="wubeLogo" />
        </creator>

        <creator id="mojang">
            <name>Mojang studios</name>
            <description>
                Mojang is a Swedish video game developer and publisher. It is best known for developing the popular game "Minecraft."

            </description>
            <logo src="mojangLogo" />
        </creator>

        <creator id="microsoft">
            <name>Microsoft</name>
            <description>
                Microsoft Corporation is an American multinational technology company known for developing, licensing, and selling computer
                software, consumer electronics, and other services.
            </description>
            <logo src="microsoftLogo" />
        </creator>

        <creator id="dragonBox">
            <name>Kahoot and DragonBox</name>
            <description>
                Kahoot in colaboration with DragonBox is a game development studio that focuses on creating educational games to make
                learning fun and engaging for students of all ages.
            </description>
            <logo src="dragonBoxLogo" />
        </creator>
    </creators>

    <games>
        <game id="reMission2" genreRef="gamesForHealth" alluvialAreaRef="healthcare" creatorRef="hopelab">
            <title>Re-Mission 2</title>
            <description>
                Designed for young cancer patients, this game aims to teach them about cancer and its treatment in an engaging way.
                Players control a nanobot named Roxxi to fight cancer cells.
            </description>
            <releaseDate>04.29.2013</releaseDate>
            <graphics>
                <coverImage src="reMission2Cover" />
                <screenshots>
                    <screenshot src="reMission2Screenshot1" />
                    <screenshot src="reMission2Screenshot2" />
                </screenshots>
            </graphics>
        </game>

        <game id="simCityEDU" genreRef="gamesForEducation" alluvialAreaRef="education" creatorRef="glasslab">
            <title>SimCityEDU: Pollution Challenge!</title>
            <description>
                This educational game challenges players to address pollution issues in a virtual city,
                teaching environmental concepts and problem-solving skills.
            </description>
            <releaseDate>07.11.2013</releaseDate>
            <graphics>
                <coverImage src="simCityCover" />
                <screenshots>
                    <screenshot src="simCityScreenshot1" />
                    <screenshot src="simCityScreenshot2" />
                </screenshots>
            </graphics>
        </game>

        <game id="foldit" genreRef="gamesForScienceAndResearch" alluvialAreaRef="governmentNgo" creatorRef="uwCse">
            <title>Foldit</title>
            <description>
                Foldit is an online puzzle video game about protein folding.
                Players can contribute to scientific research by solving complex puzzles related to protein structure and function.
            </description>
            <releaseDate>08.05.2008</releaseDate>
            <graphics>
                <coverImage src="folditCover" />
                <screenshots>
                    <screenshot src="folditScreenshot1" />
                    <screenshot src="folditScreenshot2" />
                </screenshots>
            </graphics>
        </game>

        <game id="factorio" genreRef="gamesForProduction" alluvialAreaRef="industry" creatorRef="wubeSoftware">
            <title>Factorio</title>
            <description>
                Factorio is a real-time strategy game focused on resource management and automation.
                Players work to build and manage factories, optimizing production processes and dealing with challenges in a complex environment.
            </description>
            <releaseDate>25.02.2016</releaseDate>
            <graphics>
                <coverImage src="factorioCover" />
                <screenshots>
                    <screenshot src="factorioScreenshot1" />
                    <screenshot src="factorioScreenshot2" />
                </screenshots>
            </graphics>
        </game>

        <game id="minecraft" genreRef="gamesForEducation" alluvialAreaRef="education" creatorRef="mojang">
            <title>Minecraft</title>
            <description>
                "Minecraft" is a sandbox game that allows players to build and explore virtual worlds made up of blocks.
                It offers creative and survival modes, encouraging creativity and collaboration.
            </description>
            <releaseDate>11.11.2011</releaseDate>
            <graphics>
                <coverImage src="minecraftCover" />
                <screenshots>
                    <screenshot src="minecraftScreenshot1" />
                    <screenshot src="minecraftScreenshot2" />
                </screenshots>
            </graphics>
        </game>

        <game id="flightSimulator" genreRef="gamesForTraining" alluvialAreaRef="defense" creatorRef="microsoft">
            <title>Microsoft Flight Simulator</title>
            <description>
                "Microsoft Flight Simulator" is a flight simulation game that offers a realistic and detailed representation of various
                aircraft and landscapes. It provides an immersive experience for aviation enthusiasts.
            </description>
            <releaseDate>18.08.2020</releaseDate>
            <graphics>
                <coverImage src="flightSimulatorCover" />
                <screenshots>
                    <screenshot src="flightSimulatorScreenshot1" />
                    <screenshot src="flightSimulatorScreenshot2" />
                </screenshots>
            </graphics>
        </game>

        <game id="dragonBoxElements" genreRef="gamesForEducation" alluvialAreaRef="education" creatorRef="dragonBox">
            <title>DragonBox Elements</title>
            <description>
                "DragonBox Elements" is an educational game that teaches geometry concepts in a fun and interactive way.
                It is designed to make learning math enjoyable for students.
            </description>
            <releaseDate>14.05.2014</releaseDate>
            <graphics>
                <coverImage src="dragonBoxElementsCover" />
                <screenshots>
                    <screenshot src="dragonBoxElementsScreenshot1" />
                    <screenshot src="dragonBoxElementsScreenshot2" />
                </screenshots>
            </graphics>
        </game>
    </games>
</seriousGamesCatalog>